♪I've braved the storms, walked through the rain♪
لقد تحديت العواصف، وسرت تحت المطر
♪Seen the highs and lows along the way♪
♪لقد رأيت الارتفاعات والانخفاضات على طول الطريق♪
♪But you stay quiet, never change♪
♪لكنك تبقى هادئًا، ولا تتغير أبدًا♪
♪Like a child who dreams beneath the stars♪
♪مثل طفل يحلم تحت النجوم♪
♪I've read the story in your eyes♪
♪لقد قرأت القصة في عينيك♪
♪And finally, nothing's left to hide♪
♪وأخيرًا، لم يعد هناك ما نخفيه♪
♪You won't give in to a world so cold♪
♪لن تستسلم لعالم بارد جدًا♪
♪So you wander through it on your own♪
♪لذا تتجول فيه بمفردك♪
♪Maybe fate has drawn us near♪
ربما يكون القدر قد قربنا
♪Just to help you learn to believe♪
♪فقط لمساعدتك على تعلم الإيمان♪
♪Everything you've questioned deep inside♪
♪كل ما تساءلت عنه في أعماقك♪
♪I'll be the proof you need♪
♪سأكون الدليل الذي تحتاجه♪
♪I've made my choice♪
♪لقد اتخذت قراري♪
♪For you, I'll be brave and break the rules♪
♪من أجلك، سأكون شجاعًا وأكسر القواعد♪
♪What's there to fear even if the world is right and I am wrong?♪
♪ما الذي يجب أن تخاف منه حتى لو كان العالم على حق وأنا على خطأ؟♪
♪One day, all of this will turn into memories♪
♪في يوم من الأيام، كل هذا سوف يتحول إلى ذكريات♪
♪Every storm we faced will turn into our life's scenery♪
♪كل عاصفة نواجهها سوف تتحول إلى مشهد حياتنا♪
♪For you, I'll be brave and break the rules♪
♪من أجلك، سأكون شجاعًا وأكسر القواعد♪
♪What's there to fear even if the world is right and I am wrong?♪
♪ما الذي يجب أن تخاف منه حتى لو كان العالم على حق وأنا على خطأ؟♪
♪Even if, in the end, the whole world turns against me♪
♪حتى لو تحول العالم كله ضدي في النهاية♪
♪I won't regret having loved you♪
♪لن أندم على حبي لك♪
♪With all my heart♪
♪من كل قلبي♪
♪I've held you close♪
لقد احتضنتك بقوة
♪Walked by your side♪
♪مشيت بجانبك♪
♪And loved the fire that burned inside you♪
♪وأحببت النار التي اشتعلت بداخلك♪
[The First Frost]
[الصقيع الأول]
[Adapted from the novel of the same name by Zhu Yi on www.jjwxc.net]
[مقتبس من رواية تحمل نفس الاسم بقلم تشو يي على www.jjwxc.net]
[Yihe University]
[جامعة ييهي]
Wen Yifan,
وين ييفان،
what are you doing here in the middle of the night?
ماذا تفعل هنا في منتصف الليل؟
You scared me!
لقد اخافتني!
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Yifan, you have an exam tomorrow.
ييفان، لديك امتحان غدا.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Yifan?
ييفان؟
Why aren't you moving?
لماذا لا تتحرك؟
Wen Yifan, I'm talking to you.
وين ييفان، أنا أتحدث إليك.
Yifan?
ييفان؟
Come with me to the bathroom. I'm scared.
تعال معي إلى الحمام، أنا خائفة.
Okay, wait for me.
حسنًا، انتظرني.
We agreed to go to a social event to relax together
لقد اتفقنا على الذهاب إلى مناسبة اجتماعية للاسترخاء معًا
after the exam.
بعد الامتحان
If you don't go, we'll be one person short.
إذا لم تذهب، سوف ينقصنا شخص واحد.
Please,
لو سمحت،
just go with us.
فقط اذهب معنا.
I was so scared last night...
لقد كنت خائفة جدًا الليلة الماضية...
I couldn't sleep well.
لم أستطع النوم جيدا.
And we have an exam in the morning.
وعندنا امتحان في الصباح.
I'm really tired.
أنا متعب حقا.
Hurry up,
اسرعي
the guys are already rushing us.
الرجال يسرعون إلينا بالفعل.
Why don't you ask her?
لماذا لا تسألها؟
Hurry, go!
اسرع اذهب!
Well, Yifan.
حسنًا، ييفان.
You must be bored sitting alone in the dorm.
لابد أنك تشعر بالملل من الجلوس بمفردك في السكن.
Why not come with us?
لماذا لا تأتي معنا؟
Right, come with us.
حسنا، تعال معنا.
Otherwise, you'll be out of the group.
وإلا سوف تكون خارج المجموعة.
Go on.
إستمر.
- Really? - Love you!
- حقا؟ - أحبك!
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Yifan,
ييفان،
do you usually like watching movies?
هل تحب عادة مشاهدة الأفلام؟
There's a new
هناك جديد
romantic movie coming out.
فيلم رومانسي قادم.
Great.
عظيم.
I want to watch a movie, too!
أريد أن أشاهد فيلماً أيضاً!
I love watching movies, too!
أنا أيضا أحب مشاهدة الأفلام!
Let's go together.
دعنا نذهب معا.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Who wants to go with you?
من يريد الذهاب معك؟
Go have fun with someone else.
اذهب واستمتع مع شخص آخر.
I also like romantic movies.
أنا أيضا أحب الأفلام الرومانسية.
Yifan,
ييفان،
have you decided where to intern?
هل قررت أين ستتدرب؟
You need to start making decisions now.
يجب عليك البدء في اتخاذ القرارات الآن.
Otherwise, you won't find a good internship.
وإلا فلن تجد تدريبًا جيدًا.
Right.
يمين.
If you want to go to a newspaper office,
إذا كنت تريد الذهاب إلى مكتب الصحيفة،
my uncle can arrange it.
عمي يستطيع ترتيب ذلك.
Really?
حقًا؟
The radio station is also nice.
محطة الراديو جميلة أيضاً.
I know someone
انا اعرف شخص ما
from Yihe Radio Station.
من محطة إذاعة ييهي.
Yifan,
ييفان،
if you're interested,
إذا كنت مهتما،
I can introduce you to them.
أستطيع أن أقدمهم لك.
I'd also like to go there.
وأود أن أذهب إلى هناك أيضًا.
These days,
في هذه الأيام،
who still reads newspapers or listens to the radio?
من لا يزال يقرأ الصحف أو يستمع إلى الراديو؟
It's outdated.
لقد أصبح قديما.
Can you introduce me?
هل يمكنك أن تقدمني؟
I still need to call my family tonight,
لا أزال بحاجة إلى الاتصال بعائلتي الليلة،
so I'll skip eating.
لذلك سأتوقف عن الأكل.
Enjoy your meal.
أتمنى لك وجبة شهية.
I'll see you out.
سأراك خارجا.
- Take care, Yifan. - I'll call a cab for you.
- اعتني بنفسك يا ييفان. - سأطلب لك سيارة أجرة.
Make sure to stay safe.
تأكد من البقاء آمنًا.
Bye!
الوداع!
Yifan, goodbye!
ييفان، وداعا!
Yifan, stay safe!
ييفان، ابقى آمنًا!
Eat up.
تناول الطعام.
This is pretty good.
هذا جيد جدًا.
Eat more.
تناول المزيد.
Why are you so interested in Wen Yifan?
لماذا أنت مهتم جدًا بـ وين ييفان؟
She's the prettiest in our department.
إنها الأجمل في قسمنا.
[Bai Jiang] Long time no see. You're finally online.
[باي جيانج] لم نلتقي منذ فترة طويلة، أنت متصل بالإنترنت أخيرًا.
How's everything?
كيف الحال؟
I've been busy with my lessons.
لقد كنت مشغولاً بدروسي.
[Warm Water] By the way, do you know
[ماء دافئ] بالمناسبة، هل تعلم؟
how to pass the "King No.4" level in the game?
كيفية اجتياز مستوى "الملك رقم 4" في اللعبة؟
[Bai Jiang] I know. Let me teach you.
[باي جيانج] أعلم ذلك، دعني أعلمك.
[You've earned one "King No.4" badge] I passed.
[لقد حصلت على شارة "الملك رقم 4"] لقد نجحت.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
[Bai Jiang] Congratulations on clearing it.
[باي جيانج] مبروك على إتمام الأمر.
[Warm Water] I originally thought
[ماء دافئ] كنت أعتقد في الأصل
tonight's dinner would be a nightmare,
سيكون عشاء الليلة بمثابة كابوس،
but luckily, I have you.
ولكن لحسن الحظ، لدي أنت.
I feel much better now.
أشعر بتحسن كبير الآن.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I'm logging off now.
سأقوم بتسجيل الخروج الآن.
Go to bed early. Good night.
اذهب إلى النوم مبكرًا. تصبح على خير.
Sang Yan,
سانج يان
why aren't you asleep yet?
لماذا لم تنام بعد؟
[Episode 22] [Opportunity]
[الحلقة 22] [الفرصة]
[3445 days]
[3445 يوما]
Grandma,
الجدة
you must have gained a lot from this trip.
لا بد أنك استفدت كثيرًا من هذه الرحلة.
If I have the chance, I'd like to do a road trip
إذا أتيحت لي الفرصة، أود أن أقوم برحلة برية
like you.
مثلك.
Great.
عظيم.
I'll organize my maps
سأقوم بتنظيم خرائطي
and all the travel guidances I've collected,
وكل إرشادات السفر التي جمعتها،
and give them to you once I'm done.
وأعطيهم لك عندما أنتهي منهم.
That's great! Thanks, Grandma.
هذا رائع! شكرا لك يا جدتي.
Actually, you could ask me to go with you.
في الواقع، يمكنك أن تطلب مني أن أذهب معك.
It's so boring alone.
إنه أمر ممل جدًا أن أكون وحدي.
Really?
حقًا؟
Grandma,
الجدة
did you ever feel lonely during your trip?
هل شعرت بالوحدة يومًا أثناء رحلتك؟
Well, loneliness
حسنا، الوحدة
is inevitable at times.
أمر لا مفر منه في بعض الأحيان.
But I think, in life,
ولكنني أعتقد أنه في الحياة،
everyone has a time
كل شخص لديه وقت
when they should be alone.
عندما يجب عليهم أن يكونوا بمفردهم.
The philosopher Kant once said,
لقد قال الفيلسوف كانط ذات مرة:
"I am lonely.
"أنا وحيد.
I am free.
أنا حر.
But I am my own king."
"ولكن أنا ملكي الخاص."
This trip,
هذه الرحلة،
I really learned a lot.
لقد تعلمت الكثير حقا.
I also learned a lot.
لقد تعلمت الكثير أيضاً.
I learned
لقد تعلمت
to embrace solitude at home.
احتضان العزلة في المنزل.
But,
لكن،
to be honest,
صراحة،
when you weren't home,
عندما لم تكن في المنزل،
I often
انا في كثير من الأحيان
woke up from nightmares
استيقظت من الكوابيس
in the middle of the night.
في منتصف الليل.
I just worry
أنا فقط أشعر بالقلق
if something happened to you.
إذا حدث لك شيء.
Sometimes,
أحيانا،
I messaged her, but she didn't reply.
لقد أرسلت لها رسالة ولكنها لم ترد.
Oh,
أوه،
I was driving.
كنت أقود السيارة.
How could I use my phone?
كيف يمكنني استخدام هاتفي؟
I knew it.
كنت أعرف.
So, I got used to it later.
لذا، اعتدت على ذلك لاحقًا.
Also,
أيضًا،
when you weren't around,
عندما لم تكن موجودا،
I often think about the happy moments
أفكر كثيرًا في اللحظات السعيدة
we had before.
لقد كان لدينا من قبل.
And,
و،
Grandpa wrote down all the important things
كتب الجد كل الأشياء المهمة
in a little notebook.
في دفتر صغير.
So, how could you forget?
فكيف يمكنك أن تنسى؟
Right?
يمين؟
Exactly.
بالضبط.
On this lonely trip,
في هذه الرحلة الوحيدة،
I realized
لقد ادركت
you old man
انت رجل عجوز
are still very important to me.
لا تزال مهمة جدًا بالنسبة لي.
It has never changed.
لم يتغير أبدًا.
Grandma,
الجدة
which stop on this trip
التي تتوقف في هذه الرحلة
impressed you the most?
ما الذي أعجبك أكثر؟
Let me think.
دعني أفكر.
I went to the place
ذهبت إلى المكان
where your father, mother,
أين والدك، أمك،
and your brother had the accident.
وأخوك تعرض للحادث.
It was so empty,
لقد كان فارغا جدا،
yet so beautiful.
ولكنها جميلة جداً.
I spent the whole day there.
لقد قضيت اليوم كله هناك.
I stayed there
بقيت هناك
from morning till night.
من الصباح حتى الليل.
Did you see it?
هل رأيته؟
I didn't expect
لم اتوقع
that after all these years,
أنه بعد كل هذه السنوات،
this place has become even more beautiful.
لقد أصبح هذا المكان أكثر جمالا.
If we get the chance,
إذا حصلنا على الفرصة،
I'll bring you all here again.
سأحضركم جميعا هنا مرة أخرى.
How about that?
ماذا عن ذلك؟
Going back there,
العودة إلى هناك،
you must have been so sad.
لا بد وأنك كنت حزينًا جدًا.
I was thinking,
كنت أفكر
ten years
عشر سنوات
have gone by,
لقد مرت
and our whole family
وكل عائلتنا
has never mentioned the accident.
لم يذكر الحادث مطلقا.
I'll go slice some fruit.
سأذهب لتقطيع بعض الفاكهة.
No need!
لا حاجة!
Come.
يأتي.
Sit down.
اجلس.
We should have a serious talk.
ينبغي علينا أن نجري محادثة جادة.
Okay.
تمام.
After the accident,
بعد الحادث،
our whole family has been silent about it.
لقد التزمت عائلتنا بأكملها الصمت بشأن هذا الأمر.
But actually, it's been stuck in our hearts.
لكن في الواقع، فقد ظلت عالقة في قلوبنا.
We can't forget it,
لا يمكننا أن ننسى ذلك،
but
لكن
we're also avoiding it.
ونحن نتجنبه أيضًا.
I was just thinking,
كنت أفكر فقط،
how nice it is
كم هو جميل
that I still have you all!
أنني لا أزال أملككم جميعا!
We need to live well!
نحن بحاجة للعيش جيدا!
We need to forget all the sad things
نحن بحاجة إلى أن ننسى كل الأشياء الحزينة
one by one.
واحدا تلو الآخر.
Is that okay?
هل هذا جيد؟
Okay.
تمام.
I'm ready now. I'm coming over.
أنا مستعد الآن، أنا قادم.
I've been drinking.
لقد كنت أشرب.
Should I have someone pick you up?
هل يجب أن أطلب من شخص أن يقلك؟
No, I'll come over myself.
لا، سأأتي بنفسي.
Be careful on your way.
كن حذرا في طريقك.
Yifan, bye.
ييفان، وداعا.
- Bye. - Bye, Yifan.
- وداعا. - وداعا، ييفان.
See you later.
أراك لاحقًا.
Yifan.
ييفان.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
You look so pretty today.
أنت تبدو جميلة جدًا اليوم.
I'm going to attend
انا سوف احضر
a friend's wedding banquet.
حفل زفاف صديق.
I have something to tell you.
عندي شيء أريد أن أخبرك به.
I'll go down with you.
سأنزل معك.
But now that you two are together,
ولكن الآن بعد أن أصبحتما معًا،
there's something I want to explain to you.
هناك شيء أريد أن أشرحه لك.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
what I said before
ما قلته من قبل
about Sang Yan's speech at the graduation ceremony
حول خطاب سانغ يان في حفل التخرج
was all made up by me.
كان كل ذلك من صنعي.
At the graduation dinner,
في حفل التخرج،
someone asked Sang Yan,
سأل أحدهم سانج يان،
"Is what's unattainable always the best,
"إن ما لا يمكن تحقيقه هو الأفضل دائمًا،
and is that why you're so sad?"
وهل هذا هو السبب الذي يجعلك حزينًا جدًا؟
He said,
وقال:
"Do you think I could be that devoted?"
هل تعتقد أنني يمكن أن أكون مخلصًا إلى هذه الدرجة؟
But there really was a senior who said
ولكن كان هناك بالفعل شخص كبير السن قال
he had been a backup for years.
لقد كان احتياطيًا لسنوات.
But I can't really remember the details.
ولكنني لا أستطيع أن أتذكر التفاصيل حقًا.
I was unsure how to face you
لم أكن متأكدًا من كيفية مواجهتك
because of this.
بسبب هذا.
But now, I've come to terms with it.
ولكن الآن، لقد تصالحت مع الأمر.
Why are you saying this now?
لماذا تقول هذا الآن؟
Because I'm afraid
لأني خائف
those words might affect your relationship.
قد تؤثر هذه الكلمات على علاقتك.
They won't.
لن يفعلوا ذلك.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
I wish you a future
أتمنى لك مستقبلا
without pressure,
بدون ضغط
whether it's in work,
سواء كان ذلك في العمل،
life,
حياة،
or relationships.
أو العلاقات.
Actually, I think
في الواقع، أعتقد
sometimes it's fine to just let things be.
في بعض الأحيان يكون من الجيد ترك الأمور كما هي.
I wish you happiness.
أتمنى لك السعادة.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You, too.
أنت أيضاً.
Enjoy your meal.
أتمنى لك وجبة شهية.
Take your time.
خذ وقتك.
Guys,
شباب،
let me introduce
دعني أقدم لك
today's leading lady,
سيدة اليوم الرائدة
my wife, Shiwen.
زوجتي شيوين.
Hello, everyone.
أهلا بالجميع.
These are my colleagues from the restaurant,
هؤلاء هم زملائي من المطعم،
and these are my college roommates.
وهؤلاء هم زملائي في الكلية.
We're all really good friends.
نحن جميعا أصدقاء جيدين حقا.
Why does she look so familiar?
لماذا تبدو مألوفة جداً؟
Stop seeking attention, Chen Junwen.
توقف عن البحث عن الاهتمام، تشين جون وين.
But he's the matchmaker.
لكن هو الخاطبة.
Without him,
بدونه،
we wouldn't be together.
لن نكون معاً
Thanks a lot.
شكرًا جزيلاً.
I'll drink with you more later, okay?
سأشرب معك أكثر في وقت لاحق، حسنًا؟
Enjoy your meal, Miss.
استمتعي بوجبتك يا آنسة.
Sorry, I'm late.
عذرا لقد تأخرت.
Did I miss something?
هل فاتني شيء؟
You came at just the right time.
لقد أتيت في الوقت المناسب.
Let's drink more later.
دعونا نشرب المزيد في وقت لاحق.
I'll go greet others.
سأذهب لتحية الآخرين.
Where have you been for so long?
أين كنت طوال هذه المدة؟
How dare you be late on such an important day?
كيف تجرؤ على التأخر في مثل هذا اليوم المهم؟
Take a taxi back to Yihe now!
خذ سيارة أجرة للعودة إلى ييهي الآن!
Su Haoan,
سو هاوان،
you've had quite a lot of issues with me lately.
لقد كانت لديك الكثير من المشاكل معي في الآونة الأخيرة.
It's just because you're too handsome.
هذا فقط لأنك وسيم جدًا.
This is Duan Jiaxu, right?
هذا دوان جياكسو، أليس كذلك؟
Didn't you meet him last time?
ألم تقابله في المرة الماضية؟
He's quite handsome.
إنه وسيم جدًا.
He hasn't changed much.
لم يتغير كثيرا .
Is he handsome?
هل هو وسيم؟
This picture is pretty average.
هذه الصورة متوسطة جدًا.
He looks a bit dull.
إنه يبدو مملًا بعض الشيء.
Yu Zhuo,
يو تشو،
is he handsome?
هل هو وسيم؟
Let me check properly.
دعني أتحقق بشكل صحيح.
You're not really in love with Duan Jiaxu, are you?
أنت لست في الواقع في حب دوان جياكسو، أليس كذلك؟
Su Haoan,
سو هاوان،
is he handsome?
هل هو وسيم؟
He's just okay.
إنه بخير فقط.
He's not even a fraction as handsome as me.
إنه ليس وسيمًا مثلي حتى ولو قليلاً.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
I can tell now.
أستطيع أن أقول الآن.
No wonder you blush every time you see me.
لا عجب أنك تخجل في كل مرة تراني.
Thanks. I'm going to throw up.
شكرا. سأتقيأ.
But you haven't even drunk yet.
ولكنك لم تشرب بعد.
Chen Junwen.
تشين جون وين.
What?
ماذا؟
Is he handsome?
هل هو وسيم؟
- Of course, he's handsome. - I mean...
- بالطبع، إنه وسيم. - أعني...
Who's handsomer, him or me?
من هو الأجمل هو أم أنا؟
Well, obviously, Jiaxu is more handsome.
حسنًا، من الواضح أن جياكسو أكثر وسامة.
There's no doubt about it.
لا شك في ذلك.
Have you eaten enough?
هل أكلت بما فيه الكفاية؟
If so, head home.
إذا كان الأمر كذلك، توجه إلى المنزل.
Duan Jiaxu,
دوآن جياكسو،
you haven't drunk.
لم تشرب.
Later, take my sister back home.
لاحقًا، خذ أختي إلى المنزل.
I just got here.
لقد وصلت هنا للتو.
Don't mind him.
لا تهتم به.
I've thought it through.
لقد فكرت في الأمر جيدًا.
There's the fairest way.
هذه هي الطريقة الأكثر عدالة.
I'll count to three,
سأحسب إلى ثلاثة،
and we'll pick the most handsome one we think.
وسوف نختار الشخص الأكثر وسامة في رأينا.
How about it?
ماذا عن ذلك؟
Okay.
تمام.
- It's fair. - Come on.
- إنه عادل. - هيا.
One.
واحد.
Two.
اثنين.
Three!
ثلاثة!
Call me when you're here.
اتصل بي عندما تكون هنا.
Sang Yan,
سانج يان
is your girlfriend coming or not?
هل صديقتك قادمة أم لا؟
You've been hiding her for so long.
لقد كنت تخفيها لفترة طويلة.
Or...
أو...
did you just make this up?
هل اخترعت هذا للتو؟
I think so.
أعتقد ذلك.
Yeah, boss.
نعم يا رئيس.
Will she really come?
هل ستأتي حقا؟
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Will she come or not?
هل ستأتي أم لا؟
Look,
ينظر،
he's on the phone.
إنه على الهاتف.
I'm getting in the car now.
سأدخل إلى السيارة الآن.
I'll go find you directly.
سأذهب للبحث عنك مباشرة.
Let's wait and see.
دعونا ننتظر ونرى.
Let's look forward to it.
دعونا نتطلع إلى ذلك.
What's up? The delivery's here?
ما الأمر؟ هل تم التسليم هنا؟
What did you order?
ماذا طلبت؟
Share with us.
شارك معنا.
Takeout?
أخرج؟
After the banquet, I'll drive you home.
بعد المأدبة، سأوصلك إلى المنزل.
Okay.
تمام.
Let's go, sir.
دعنا نذهب يا سيدي.
Stop here, thanks.
توقف هنا، شكرًا لك.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
I've been waiting for you.
لقد كنت في انتظارك.
Have you drunk?
هل شربت؟
Anyone with a girlfriend had to drink.
كان على أي شخص لديه صديقة أن يشرب.
Will I have to drink, too?
هل سأضطر للشرب أيضًا؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
But,
لكن،
your boyfriend here has already taken care of that for you.
لقد قام صديقك هنا بالفعل برعاية هذا الأمر من أجلك.
How much did you drink?
كم شربت؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
I really don't know my limits.
أنا حقا لا أعرف حدودي.
Sang Yan,
سانج يان
so your girlfriend is Wen Yifan?
إذن صديقتك هي وين ييفان؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
She's the one you've been talking about,
إنها الشخص الذي كنت تتحدث عنه
the girl who's been madly flirting with you?
الفتاة التي كانت تغازلك بجنون؟
You actually said that?
هل قلت ذلك فعلا؟
Where's Duan Jiaxu?
أين دوان جياكسو؟
Duan Jiaxu didn't drink.
لم يشرب دوآن جياكسو.
So he took Sang Zhi home.
فأخذ سانج تشي إلى منزله.
How can Duan Jiaxu miss
كيف يمكن لدوان جياكسو أن يخطئ؟
such an absurd lie he told?
هذه كذبة سخيفة قالها؟
Wen Yifan, say something.
وين ييفان، قل شيئا.
Slap his shameless face!
اصفع وجهه الوقح!
Look at him now,
أنظر إليه الآن،
so arrogant and self-righteous.
متغطرس ومتغطرس.
So disgusting!
مقزز للغاية!
I do admit,
انا أعترف بذلك
but it's not about flirting,
لكن الأمر لا يتعلق بالمغازلة،
It's about pursuing.
إن الأمر يتعلق بالمتابعة.
Su Haoan,
سو هاوان،
you said
أنت قلت
there was a girl Sang Yan couldn't get
كانت هناك فتاة لم يستطع سانج يان الحصول عليها
back in high school.
العودة إلى المدرسة الثانوية.
So, that girl is...
إذن تلك الفتاة هي...
Yes.
نعم.
Honestly,
بصدق،
when Sang Yan asked me
عندما سألني سانج يان
if Duan Jiaxu was handsome,
إذا كان دوان جياكسو وسيمًا،
I felt quite strange.
لقد شعرت بغرابة شديدة.
"Who's handsomer,
"من هو الأكثر وسامة،
Duan Jiaxu or me?"
دوآن جياكسو أم أنا؟"
I vote for you.
انا اصوت لك
No need.
لا حاجة.
I never
انا لم افعل ذلك ابدا
force others to make their choices.
إجبار الآخرين على اتخاذ خياراتهم.
I'm sincere.
انا صادقة.
Really?
حقًا؟
Otherwise, I wouldn't
وإلا فلن أفعل ذلك
have pursued you so crazily.
لقد طاردتك بجنون.
♪I've made my choice...♪
♪لقد اتخذت قراري...♪
Oh my god!
يا إلهي!
Cheers to you two!
شكرا لكما!
I'll change the wedding photo right away,
سأغير صورة الزفاف على الفور،
and you two just get married here today.
و أنتما الاثنان ستتزوجان هنا اليوم.
Is that okay?
هل هذا جيد؟
Congratulations.
مبروك.
They came here today
لقد جاؤوا هنا اليوم
just to disgust us.
فقط لإثارة اشمئزازنا.
I really don't get it.
انا حقا لا أفهم ذلك.
♪What's there to fear even if the world is right and I am wrong?♪
♪ما الذي يجب أن تخاف منه حتى لو كان العالم على حق وأنا على خطأ؟♪
♪Even if, in the end, the whole world turns against me♪
♪حتى لو تحول العالم كله ضدي في النهاية♪
♪I won't regret having loved you♪
♪لن أندم على حبي لك♪
♪With all my heart♪
♪من كل قلبي♪
♪I've held you close, walked by your side♪
لقد احتضنتك ومشيت بجانبك
♪And loved the fire that burned inside you♪
♪وأحببت النار التي اشتعلت بداخلك♪
Qian Fei
تشيان فيي
is actually the first to get married in our class.
هو في الواقع أول من تزوج في صفنا.
Right. We've been out of college for years.
حسنًا، لقد تخرجنا من الكلية منذ سنوات.
Do you remember
هل تذكر
what happened at our graduation dinner?
ماذا حدث في حفل التخرج لدينا؟
He got drunk and embarrassed himself so much.
لقد سكر وأحرج نفسه كثيرًا.
He kept complaining about himself,
ظل يشكو من نفسه،
saying how long he's been a backup.
قائلا منذ متى كان احتياطيًا.
Do you remember that?
هل تتذكر ذلك؟
Wan Lin,
وان لين
was I just your backup for four years in college?
هل كنت مجرد نسخة احتياطية لك لمدة أربع سنوات في الكلية؟
Bro.
أخ.
Wan Lin...
وان لين...
You've got drunk again.
لقد سكرت مرة أخرى.
That's not Wan Lin. You've got the wrong person.
هذا ليس وان لين، لقد أخطأت في اختيار الشخص المناسب.
Come over here.
تعال إلى هنا.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
This is Wan Lin...
هذا وان لين...
This isn't Wan Lin either.
وهذا ليس وان لين أيضًا.
Wan Lin...
وان لين...
Wan Lin's not here. Hey...
وان لين ليس هنا. مهلا...
Wan Lin,
وان لين
for four years in college,
لمدة أربع سنوات في الكلية،
was I really your backup?
هل كنت حقا نسخة احتياطية لك؟
Every time he gets drunk, he acts like this. Here.
كلما سكر يتصرف هكذا هنا
Am I just your backup...
هل أنا مجرد نسخة احتياطية لك...
No?
لا؟
- Don't move. - Wen Yifan?
- لا تتحرك. - وين ييفان؟
Shut your mouth.
اصمت.
Shut up.
اسكت.
No more talking.
لا مزيد من الحديث.
Am I just your backup?
هل أنا مجرد نسخة احتياطية لك؟
Sleep!
ينام!
Backup is fine.
النسخ الاحتياطي جيد.
Beauty, sorry.
الجمال، آسف.
Sorry, I mistook you.
عذرا لقد اخطأت في فهمك.
You two need to calm down, okay?
يجب عليكما أن تهدأا، حسنًا؟
Qian Fei!
تشيان فيي!
Come here!
تعال الى هنا!
- Come here. - Sit here.
- تعال هنا. - اجلس هنا.
Didn't Sang Yan say so?
ألم يقل سانغ يان ذلك؟
Stop talking bad about me.
توقف عن التحدث بالسوء عني.
Sang Yan was also drunk at the time.
وكان سانغ يان أيضًا في حالة سكر في ذلك الوقت.
He sat there.
كان يجلس هناك.
I don't know if he mistook me
لا أعلم إن كان قد أخطأ في فهمي
for someone else.
لشخص آخر.
He kept mumbling.
لقد ظل يتمتم.
Mumbling?
تتمتم؟
Wen Yifan,
وين ييفان،
here, let me toast to you.
هنا، اسمحوا لي أن أشرب نخبًا لك.
Congratulations on you and Sang Yan being together.
أهنئك على كونك أنت وسانغ يان معًا.
Bro, you're crushing me.
يا أخي، أنت تسحقني.
Everyone who's single should drink.
يجب على كل شخص أعزب أن يشرب.
I'm not drinking.
انا لا اشرب.
Right, Wen Yifan must drink.
حسنًا، يجب على وين ييفان أن يشرب.
[Qian Fei &amp; Zeng Shiwen]
[تشيان فيي و زينج شيوين]
Where are we going?
إلى أين نحن ذاهبون؟
Going back home.
العودة إلى المنزل.
I can't walk anymore...
لم أعد أستطيع المشي بعد الآن...
Wen Shuangjiang,
وين شوانغجيانغ،
you've really learned something.
لقد تعلمت شيئا حقا.
You drank so much!
لقد شربت كثيرا!
Su Haoan made me drink...
سو هاوان جعلني أشرب...
That little brat.
هذا الطفل الصغير.
Stand up straight!
قف بشكل مستقيم!
Stand straight!
قف مستقيما!
I want to squat...
أريد أن أجلس القرفصاء...
Hold it steady.
ابقها ثابتة.
Two minutes.
دقيقتان.
The taxi will be here in two minutes.
سوف تصل سيارة الأجرة هنا خلال دقيقتين.
I can't stand properly...
لا أستطيع الوقوف بشكل صحيح...
Sang Yan.
سانج يان.
Sang Yan,
سانج يان
has it been tough for you all these years?
هل كان الأمر صعبًا عليك كل هذه السنوات؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Who told you something?
من قال لك شيئا؟
I was thinking,
كنت أفكر
how did you end up opening a restaurant?
كيف انتهى بك الأمر إلى فتح مطعم؟
What's wrong with me?
ماذا بي؟
I'm making money now.
أنا أكسب المال الآن.
I'm saving money to support you!
أنا أدخر المال لدعمك!
Supporting me? And then?
تدعمني؟ وبعد ذلك؟
Then you'll be mine, all mine.
حينها ستكون لي، كل ملكي.
Why do you need to support me?
لماذا تحتاج إلى دعمي؟
I do.
أفعل.
You do?
أنت تفعل؟
You smiled at all other girls!
لقد ابتسمت لجميع الفتيات الأخريات!
Don't start slandering me after getting drunk.
لا تبدأ بتشويه سمعتي بعد أن سكرت.
Who did I smile at today?
من الذي ابتسمت له اليوم؟
Not today.
ليس اليوم.
Then when?
ثم متى؟
I won't say!
لن أقول!
Tell me.
أخبرني.
No!
لا!
I won't say...
لن أقول...
You...
أنت...
The first time I visited Overtime,
في المرة الأولى التي قمت فيها بزيارة Overtime،
you smiled at four girls in one night!
ابتسمت لأربع فتيات في ليلة واحدة!
And you even added them on WeChat.
وقمت أيضًا بإضافتهم على WeChat.
I added them on WeChat?
أضفتهم على WeChat؟
Sir.
سيد.
Look for yourself.
ابحث عن نفسك
Did I add them?
هل أضفتهم؟
Get in the car.
أدخل إلى السيارة.
Where are their WeChat accounts?
أين حساباتهم على WeChat؟
Lower your head.
أخفض رأسك.
Raise your legs.
ارفع ساقيك.
Anyway, I've already been saving money.
على أية حال، لقد قمت بالفعل بتوفير المال.
You can't keep doing this.
لا يمكنك الاستمرار في فعل هذا.
Okay.
تمام.
Sir, start the car.
سيدي، قم بتشغيل السيارة.
What's wrong with my skirt?
ما هو الخطأ في تنورتي؟
Why does it feel so uncomfortable?
لماذا أشعر بهذا القدر من عدم الارتياح؟
I can't button it.
لا أستطيع أن أزره.
Can you help me button it?
هل يمكنك مساعدتي في تثبيت الزر؟
That's not appropriate.
هذا ليس مناسبا.
Done.
منتهي.
Done?
منتهي؟
Wearing this bracelet,
ارتداء هذا السوار،
do they laugh at you, saying you look like a little girl?
هل يضحكون عليك ويقولون أنك تشبهين فتاة صغيرة؟
What's it to them?
ما الأمر بالنسبة لهم؟
Does it look good?
هل يبدو جيدا؟
Yeah, it looks good.
نعم، إنه يبدو جيدا.
Can you take tomorrow off?
هل يمكنك أن تأخذ غدا إجازة؟
Why?
لماذا؟
You're this drunk.
أنت في حالة سكر.
I'm off tomorrow.
سأغادر غدا.
You will be off,
سوف تكون خارجا
so you're messing with me tonight,
إذن أنت تمزح معي الليلة،
right?
يمين؟
What messing with you?
ماذا يحدث معك؟
I'm already
انا بالفعل
working hard to make money
العمل الجاد لكسب المال
to support you.
لدعمك.
Now, you need to let go
الآن، عليك أن تتخلى عن ذلك
of your "Star" identity.
من هويتك "النجمية".
Whatever you do for me,
مهما فعلت من أجلي،
you should feel that it's natural
يجب أن تشعر أن هذا أمر طبيعي
and willingly done.
وتم ذلك طوعا.
That makes sense,
هذا منطقي
but can you save money faster?
ولكن هل يمكنك توفير المال بشكل أسرع؟
Of course, I can.
بالطبع أستطيع.
Why are you the one picking me up?
لماذا أنت من تلتقطني؟
Didn't you order for me to come?
ألم تأمرني بالمجيء؟
Really?
حقًا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Maybe it's because I wanted to see you.
ربما لأنني أردت رؤيتك.
Sang Yan's girlfriend really is Wen Yifan.
صديقة سانج يان هي في الحقيقة وين ييفان.
They made it official.
لقد جعلوها رسمية.
You drank this much
لقد شربت هذا القدر
just for that?
فقط من أجل ذلك؟
Is it worth it?
هل يستحق ذلك؟
But I do kind of envy them.
لكنني أشعر بالحسد تجاههم إلى حد ما.
It's just nice that they're happy.
من الجميل أنهم سعداء.
What do you envy?
ماذا تحسد عليه؟
They can announce to the world
ويمكنهم الإعلان للعالم
that they're together.
أنهم معًا.
That's even more touching than a proposal.
وهذا أكثر إثارة للمشاعر من الاقتراح.
Unlike my ex-girlfriends,
على عكس صديقاتي السابقات،
who wouldn't even let me post on social media.
الذي لم يسمح لي حتى بالنشر على وسائل التواصل الاجتماعي.
I wanted us to be together!
أردت أن نكون معاً!
♪Love is the loneliest thing in the world♪
♪الحب هو الشيء الأكثر وحدة في العالم♪
♪I understand that♪
♪أنا أفهم ذلك♪
♪Yet, I still want to fall for you once more♪
♪ومع ذلك، لا أزال أريد أن أقع في حبك مرة أخرى♪
♪Lost in this uncertain world♪
♪ضائع في هذا العالم غير المؤكد♪
♪You're the moment I want to hold onto♪
♪أنت اللحظة التي أريد التمسك بها♪
♪I'm fully aware of the danger, yet I dive in willingly♪
♪أنا مدرك تمامًا للخطر، ومع ذلك أغوص فيه طواعية♪
Give me your hand.
أعطني يدك.
Take care.
يعتني.
Mind your head.
اهتم برأسك.
Get up!
استيقظ!
Good.
جيد.
Thank you, sir.
شكرا لك سيدي.
You feel like throwing up?
هل تشعر بالرغبة في التقيؤ؟
Is it okay?
هل هذا جيد؟
Seems not at all.
يبدو أنه ليس كذلك على الإطلاق.
So you definitely shouldn't rely on your looks to make a living.
لذلك لا ينبغي عليك بالتأكيد الاعتماد على مظهرك لكسب لقمة العيش.
Got it?
فهمتها؟
Got it.
فهمتها.
Do you know?
هل تعلم؟
Got it!
فهمتها!
Climb on.
تسلق.
This is the least promising route!
هذا هو الطريق الأقل وعدا!
No one pushed you to rely on your looks for a living.
لم يجبرك أحد على الاعتماد على مظهرك في معيشتك.
There is...
هنالك...
Who?
من؟
When I was in Yihe,
عندما كنت في ييهي،
I got into the news department
لقد دخلت قسم الأخبار
through campus recruitment.
من خلال التوظيف في الحرم الجامعي.
You know,
أنت تعرف،
the news department has high standards for reporters.
لدى قسم الأخبار معايير عالية للمراسلين.
But I never thought I could get in,
ولكنني لم أكن أعتقد أبدًا أنني سأتمكن من الدخول،
just gave it a try.
لقد حاولت ذلك للتو.
So I submitted my resume.
لذا قدمت سيرتي الذاتية.
And then?
وثم؟
After several months, I found out
بعد عدة أشهر، اكتشفت
that people in our department said
أن الناس في قسمنا قالوا
I only got in because I have a good relationship
لقد دخلت فقط لأن لدي علاقة جيدة
with the director.
مع المخرج.
But I didn't care what they said.
ولكنني لم أهتم بما قالوه.
After all, people can say whatever they want.
في نهاية المطاف، يمكن للناس أن يقولوا ما يريدون.
I can't control them.
لا أستطيع السيطرة عليهم.
But I didn't expect
ولكنني لم اتوقع
that the director
ان المخرج
actually liked me.
لقد اعجبني فعلا.
He said with my looks,
قال بنظراتي،
I could earn more doing anything other than being a reporter.
أستطيع أن أكسب المزيد من المال من خلال القيام بأي شيء آخر غير العمل كمراسل.
And it would be easier.
وسيكون الأمر أسهل.
He said, why did I act so high and mighty?
قال لماذا تصرفت بهذه الطريقة المتكبرة؟
I didn't like that place...
لم يعجبني هذا المكان.
Then,
ثم،
let's never go back there.
دعونا لا نعود إلى هناك أبدًا.
I don't like being talked about like that either.
أنا أيضًا لا أحب أن يتم الحديث عني بهذه الطريقة.
Don't listen to them.
لا تستمع لهم
They're insane.
إنهم مجانين.
Am I heavy?
هل أنا ثقيل؟
No, not at all.
لا، على الإطلاق.
Sang Yan...
سانغ يان...
Before I came back to Nanwu, I dreamed about you.
قبل أن أعود إلى نانوو، حلمت بك.
What did you dream about me?
ماذا حلمت بي؟
I dreamed
لقد حلمت
that you and your wife came to Yihe for your honeymoon.
أنك وزوجتك أتيتما إلى ييخه لقضاء شهر العسل.
What kind of dream is that?
ما هذا النوع من الحلم؟
Sit down.
اجلس.
You were so happy,
لقد كنت سعيدا جدا
smiling at me.
ابتسم لي.
Then, in the future,
ثم في المستقبل،
we two
نحن اثنان
will also go on a trip to Yihe.
سوف أذهب أيضًا في رحلة إلى ييهي.
Alright?
على ما يرام؟
Sorry, Sang Yan.
عذرا، سانغ يان.
What are you apologizing for?
لماذا تعتذر؟
I'm too heavy.
أنا ثقيل جداً.
Not all all.
ليس كلها كلها.
Before apologizing, you should consider
قبل الاعتذار يجب عليك أن تفكر
how much weight you're carrying.
ما هو مقدار الوزن الذي تحمله؟
Your bones hurt me.
عظامك تؤلمني.
You should eat more.
ينبغي عليك أن تأكل أكثر.
Can I lie down for a bit?
هل يمكنني الاستلقاء قليلا؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
There are stars!
هناك نجوم!
Sorry, Sang Yan.
عذرا، سانغ يان.
I've been too harsh with my words before.
لقد كنت قاسياً جداً في كلماتي من قبل.
Do you know?
هل تعلم؟
I don't like Yihe.
انا لا احب ييهي.
I don't like Beiyu either.
أنا أيضًا لا أحب بيو.
No city is a place I like.
لا يوجد مكان أحبه في أي مدينة.
And these cities don't like me.
وهذه المدن لا تحبني.
At least Nanwu has my father's grave.
على الأقل نانوو يوجد بها قبر والدي.
At least,
على الأقل،
Nanwu has someone
نانوو لديه شخص ما
I've been wanting to see,
لقد كنت أريد أن أرى،
but I've never had the courage to.
ولكن لم أملك الشجاعة أبدًا للقيام بذلك.
It's you.
إنه أنت.
Sang Yan was also drunk back then.
وكان سانغ يان أيضًا في حالة سكر في ذلك الوقت.
He was there,
لقد كان هناك
sitting,
جالس
holding his cup,
يحمل كأسه
and kept mumbling.
وظل يتمتم.
Mumbling what?
تمتمة ماذا؟
He kept saying,
لقد ظل يقول،
"Am I just your backup?"
"هل أنا مجرد نسخة احتياطية لك؟"
"Backup is fine."
"النسخ الاحتياطي جيد."
At that moment,
في تلك اللحظة،
Sang Yan's words
كلمات سانغ يان
were repeatedly striking my heart...
لقد ضربت قلبي مرارا وتكرارا ...
Am I just your backup?
هل أنا مجرد نسخة احتياطية لك؟
...over and over again.
...مرة تلو الأخرى.
I feel like I was there,
أشعر وكأنني كنت هناك،
seeing that fragile Sang Yan.
رؤية هذا الهش سانغ يان.
Am I just your backup?
هل أنا مجرد نسخة احتياطية لك؟
Get up.
استيقظ.
Don't touch me. I want to sleep!
لا تلمسني أريد أن أنام!
Don't touch me!
لا تلمسني!
If you keep touching me, I'll...
إذا واصلت لمسي، سوف...
I'll curse you!
سألعنك!
Fine.
بخير.
Curse me.
لعنني.
I'm listening.
انا أستمع.
You're a sinner,
أنت خاطئ
mad and crazy.
مجنون ومجنون.
You can barely speak properly.
بالكاد تستطيع التحدث بشكل سليم.
You can't even say it right.
لا يمكنك حتى أن تقول ذلك بشكل صحيح.
Get up.
استيقظ.
Drink this hangover soup.
اشرب هذا الحساء للتخلص من آثار الكحول.
Do you know how much I drank today?
هل تعلم كم شربت اليوم؟
I thought if I drank too much, someone would take care of me.
اعتقدت أنه إذا شربت كثيرًا، فسوف يهتم بي شخص ما.
But what happened?
ولكن ماذا حدث؟
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
That person even got angry at me.
حتى أن ذلك الشخص غضب مني.
Then just ignore her.
ثم تجاهلها فقط.
Drank it all.
شربته كله.
Take your time.
خذ وقتك.
- One more sip. - You finish the rest.
- رشفة أخرى. - أكمل الباقي.
You drank a lot, too.
لقد شربت كثيرًا أيضًا.
You still remember I drank a lot?
هل مازلت تتذكر أنني شربت كثيرًا؟
I'm sleeping...
أنا نائمة...
I'm sleeping!
أنا نائمة!
Sleep in your room.
نم في غرفتك.
Get up.
استيقظ.
No!
لا!
Wen Shuangjiang.
وين شوانغجيانغ.
Come on.
تعال.
I'm not going.
انا لا اذهب
I...
أنا...
I smell bad!
رائحتي سيئة!
Then just go take a shower.
ثم اذهب للاستحمام.
I don't want to move.
لا أريد التحرك.
Can you help me shower?
هل يمكنك مساعدتي في الاستحمام؟
I can't help you.
لا أستطيع مساعدتك.
Well,
حسنًا،
if you don't want to move someday,
إذا كنت لا تريد التحرك يومًا ما،
I can help you shower, too...
يمكنني مساعدتك في الاستحمام أيضًا...
Stop.
قف.
I don't need your help with a shower.
لا أحتاج مساعدتك في الاستحمام.
Go back to your room and sleep, okay?
ارجع إلى غرفتك ونام، حسنًا؟
Stingy.
بخيل.
I'm stingy, huh?
أنا بخيل، أليس كذلك؟
Wen Shuangjiang.
وين شوانغجيانغ.
Let's see if you regret it
دعونا نرى ما إذا كنت تندم على ذلك
after waking up tomorrow.
بعد الاستيقاظ غدا.
Then I won't shower.
إذن لن أستحم.
I'm coming to sleep with you.
أنا قادم للنوم معك.
I'll stink you out.
سأتخلص منك.
I'm not sleeping with you...
أنا لا أنام معك...
Don't try to stink me out.
لا تحاول إزعاجي.
You said I could hold you while sleeping...
لقد قلت أنني أستطيع أن أحملك أثناء النوم...
Can you give me some space?
هل يمكنك أن تعطيني بعض المساحة؟
How can I sleep
كيف يمكنني النوم
while holding you?
بينما يحملك؟
Why not?
ولم لا؟
I'm a guy.
انا رجل.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
Figure it out yourself.
اكتشف ذلك بنفسك.
Seems like it really doesn't work...
يبدو أن الأمر لا يعمل حقًا...
Let me give you a riddle.
دعني أعطيك لغزًا.
Okay.
تمام.
Dogs go "woof woof woof."
الكلاب تصدر صوت "ووف ووف ووف".
Sheep go "baa baa baa."
الأغنام تقول "باا باا باا".
What do chickens do?
ماذا تفعل الدجاجات؟
Guess.
يخمن.
Opportunity (pronounced like "chicken") is for the prepared.
الفرصة (تُنطق مثل "دجاجة") مخصصة للمستعدين.
You're so smart!
أنت ذكي جدًا!
It's really interesting.
إنه مثير للاهتمام حقا.
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
Sang Yan...
سانغ يان...
It's all my fault...
إنه خطئي كله...
I shouldn't have been avoiding you...
لا ينبغي لي أن أتجنبك...
Wen Yifan.
وين ييفان.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
You stole my words.
لقد سرقت كلماتي.
Why are you holding me while sleeping?
لماذا تحتضنني وأنت نائمة؟
I sleepwalked again?
هل مشيت أثناء النوم مرة أخرى؟
I...
أنا...
You...
أنت...
You wash it yourself.
تغسلها بنفسك.
Yeah. Well...
نعم.حسنا...
while sleepwalking,
أثناء المشي أثناء النوم،
it's normal to do strange things.
من الطبيعي أن تفعل أشياء غريبة.
It's just normal.
إنه أمر طبيعي.
Yeah, it's normal.
نعم، إنه أمر طبيعي.
Like,
يحب،
wanting me to help you shower,
أريد أن أساعدك في الاستحمام،
and wanting to help me shower, too.
وأريد أن أساعدك في الاستحمام أيضًا.
And telling lame jokes.
وإلقاء النكات السخيفة.
Like, dogs go "woof woof woof,"
مثل الكلاب التي تصدر صوت "ووف ووف ووف"
sheep go "baa baa baa,"
الأغنام تذهب "باا باا باا"
and what do chickens do?
وماذا تفعل الدجاجات؟
But you didn't help me shower.
ولكنك لم تساعدني في الاستحمام.
You've kept yourself well-protected.
لقد حافظت على نفسك محمية بشكل جيد.
Opportunity (pronounced like "chicken") is for the prepared.
الفرصة (تُنطق مثل "دجاجة") مخصصة للمستعدين.
Opportunity is for Sang Yan.
الفرصة متاحة لسانغ يان.
[Episode 22] [Opportunity is for you]
[الحلقة 22] [الفرصة متاحة لك]
[The story is not over yet...]
[القصة لم تنتهي بعد...]
Wake up.
استيقظ.
Sit up.
اجلس.
Here is your change of clothes.
وهنا تغيير الملابس الخاصة بك.
I put them here.
وضعتهم هنا.
♪Caught off guard♪
♪أُخذ على حين غرة♪
♪Meeting you made me start acting foolish♪
♪لقاءك جعلني أبدأ بالتصرف بغباء♪
♪My heart races, and even my breath pauses♪
♪يتسارع نبض قلبي، وحتى أنفاسي تتوقف♪
♪I can't control myself♪
♪لا أستطيع السيطرة على نفسي♪
♪Moving closer to you♪
♪الاقتراب منك♪
♪Step by step♪
♪خطوة بخطوة♪
♪Our relationship is spiraling out of control♪
♪علاقتنا أصبحت خارجة عن السيطرة♪
♪Dragonflies fly by, declaring love♪
♪تحلق اليعسوب، معلنة الحب♪
♪My mind is full of you♪
♪عقلي مليء بك♪
♪It becomes so clear...♪
♪يصبح الأمر واضحا جدا...♪
Sit properly.
اجلس بشكل صحيح.
I've prepared your water.
لقد قمت بإعداد الماء الخاص بك.
You can wash yourself, right?
يمكنك أن تغسل نفسك، أليس كذلك؟
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
♪I've always been cautious...♪
♪لقد كنت حذرا دائما...♪
Your lashes...
رموشك...
Take them off!
أخلعهم!
Which ones are fake?
أيهما مزيف؟
I...
أنا...
♪Like the breeze flowing through the fragrant earth...♪
♪مثل النسيم المتدفق عبر الأرض العطرة...♪
I'll pull them out, okay?
سأخرجهم، حسنًا؟
♪Like butterflies flying towards brilliant colors...♪
♪مثل الفراشات التي تطير نحو الألوان الرائعة...♪
This is fake, right?
هذا مزيف، أليس كذلك؟
♪Like a noisy afternoon suddenly turning quiet♪
♪مثل فترة ما بعد الظهر الصاخبة التي تتحول فجأة إلى هدوء♪
♪Like tears falling into the sea, escaping loneliness...♪
♪مثل الدموع التي تسقط في البحر، هربًا من الوحدة...♪
Then,
ثم،
wash yourself.
اغسل نفسك.
I'll go out.
سأخرج.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Taking shower.
الاستحمام.
Hey,
يا،
take your clothes off after I go out.
اخلع ملابسك بعد خروجي.
♪Even the strongest heart♪
♪حتى أقوى القلوب♪
♪Can waver♪
♪يمكن أن يتردد♪
♪And doubt its fire♪
♪و أشك في نارها♪
♪But you never lost faith in me♪
♪ولكنك لم تفقد الإيمان بي أبدًا♪
♪In every battle, every dream I chased♪
♪في كل معركة، وفي كل حلم سعيت لتحقيقه♪
♪There is meaning in every step I made♪
♪هناك معنى في كل خطوة اتخذتها♪
♪Through the storm, through the endless night♪
♪من خلال العاصفة، من خلال الليل الذي لا نهاية له♪
♪You were there, shining like a light♪
♪كنت هناك، تتألق مثل الضوء♪
♪Warm and bright♪
♪دافئ ومشرق♪
♪Standing right by my side♪
♪الوقوف بجانبي مباشرة♪
♪It was you, striding toward me through the storm♪
♪لقد كنت أنت، تتقدم نحوي عبر العاصفة♪
♪It was you, always cheering me on♪
♪لقد كنت أنت، الذي يشجعني دائمًا♪
♪The road is rough♪
♪الطريق وعر♪
♪The rain won't stop♪
♪المطر لن يتوقف♪
♪But with you here♪
♪ولكن معك هنا♪
♪I fear no dark♪
♪أنا لا أخاف من الظلام♪
♪Every thought, every memory is filled with you♪
♪كل فكرة وكل ذكرى مليئة بك♪
♪Marking our youth with every step we took♪
♪نترك بصمتنا على شبابنا مع كل خطوة نخطوها♪
♪When the downpour falls from the sky♪
♪عندما يهطل المطر من السماء♪
♪You're the one holding out an umbrella for me♪
♪أنت الشخص الذي يحمل لي المظلة♪
♪When the white dove brings the news♪
♪عندما تحمل الحمامة البيضاء الأخبار♪
♪You're the first I want to tell♪
♪أنت أول من أريد أن أخبره♪
♪I won't give up. I'll stay right here with you♪
♪لن أستسلم. سأبقى هنا معك♪
♪It was you, striding toward me through the storm♪
♪لقد كنت أنت، تتقدم نحوي عبر العاصفة♪
♪It was you, always cheering me on♪
♪لقد كنت أنت، الذي يشجعني دائمًا♪
♪The road is rough♪
♪الطريق وعر♪
♪The rain won't stop♪
♪المطر لن يتوقف♪
♪But with you here♪
♪ولكن معك هنا♪
♪I will never give up♪
♪لن أستسلم أبدًا♪
♪You are my courage, my hope for the sky beyond♪
♪أنت شجاعتي وأملي في السماء ما وراءها♪
♪You are my light, shining through every night♪
♪أنت نوري الذي يضيء كل ليلة♪
♪Even if I have to walk alone someday♪
♪حتى لو كان علي أن أمشي وحدي يومًا ما♪
♪I'll never truly be on my own♪
♪لن أكون وحدي أبدًا♪
♪'Cause knowing you're here♪
♪لأنني أعلم أنك هنا♪
♪I can brave the dark ahead♪
♪أستطيع أن أواجه الظلام القادم♪
[Huge thanks to everyone involved and to all the fans of The First Frost!]
[شكرًا جزيلاً لجميع المشاركين ولجميع محبي The First Frost!]
[Treat yourself well, and the world will hold more love for you!]
[عامل نفسك جيدًا، والعالم سوف يحمل لك المزيد من الحب!]